<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>asaphyuan.com</title>
    <link href="https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages" />
    <updated>2024-10-14T15:32:45-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Asaph Yuan</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages</id>

    <entry>
        <title>On Reflection</title>
        <author>
            <name>Asaph Yuan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages/on-reflection.html"/>
        <id>https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages/on-reflection.html</id>

        <updated>2024-10-13T13:44:57-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Is this a day I’d regret or be happy about when I’m&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Is this a day I’d regret or be happy about when I’m 75?</p>
<p>Relationship with God</p>
<p>Relationship with my wife</p>
<p>Relationship with kids</p>
<p>Relationship with friends</p>
<p>Physical and mental health</p>
<p>Personal development</p>
<p>Virtues, and vices</p>
<p>Evaluating my life according to my values helps me make appropriate course corrections along the way. Instead of discovering my values at the end of my life, I want to remind myself about them daily. This also helps to short-circuit the way sinful patterns work. As J.C. Ryle says, we go astray in our hearts before we do in our lives. This practice endeavors to cut the weeds of sin early before it takes over my life. I know it doesn’t prevent sin, but the daily routine forces me to keep short accounts with God and others and be honest with myself.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.thegospelcoalition.org/blogs/erik-raymond/one-question-i-ask-myself-everyday/">https://www.thegospelcoalition.org/blogs/erik-raymond/one-question-i-ask-myself-everyday/</a></p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Movies to Watch</title>
        <author>
            <name>Asaph Yuan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages/movies-to-watch.html"/>
        <id>https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages/movies-to-watch.html</id>

        <updated>2024-10-11T19:59:48-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Perfect Days Despicable Me 4 Super Man the Christopher Reeves story The&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><a href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt27503384/">Perfect Days</a></p>
<p>Despicable Me 4</p>
<p>Super Man the Christopher Reeves story</p>
<p>The Wild Robot</p>
<p>Transformers One</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>On Giving</title>
        <author>
            <name>Asaph Yuan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages/on-giving.html"/>
        <id>https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages/on-giving.html</id>

        <updated>2024-10-11T14:20:47-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Hey church fam, 1 Tim 6:17-19 17 Command those who are rich&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Hey church fam,</p>
<p>1 Tim 6:17-19<br>17 Command those who are rich in this present world not to be arrogant nor to put their hope in wealth, which is so uncertain, but to put their hope in God, who richly provides us with everything for our enjoyment. 18 Command them to do good, to be rich in good deeds, and to be generous and willing to share. 19 In this way they will lay up treasure for themselves as a firm foundation for the coming age, so that they may take hold of the life that is truly life.</p>
<p>3 things I want to point out here:</p>
<p>1. Our hope is either in wealth or in God, as Jesus mentions on the Sermon on the Mount, we cannot serve 2 masters.</p>
<p>2. We are commanded to be generous.</p>
<p>3. By doing good and being generous, we are laying up treasure as a firm foundation for the future-and it's being storing up treasure for eternity that we are truly living life.</p>
<p>When I see money leaving my bank account for my monthly giving-it’s a great moment for myself to check my heart to sense if there is joy in my giving or if there is begrudgingness. Is my hope in wealth or God?<br><br>If I feel stressed about money or annoyed that I “have” to give, I pray for a reorientation of my heart to remember what is eternal and for a grateful heart to God who has provided me ability to produce wealth.</p>
<p>2 parting thoughts:<br>1. Be generous, there’s no reason you can’t give something every month, even if it’s a dollar-it’s a command and we love Jesus by keeping His commands<br>2. When you see that money leave your bank account, reflect on the state of your heart and pray for God to orient your heart to hope even more fully on Him and to be filled with gratitude.</p>
<p>As Hue often mentions, God cares more about our will and desire becoming more like Jesus as we see Him, so my prayer is that our giving would be worship-seeing Jesus' worth and giving back a portion of what is due him.</p>
<p>Father, we invite your kingdom to grow in our hearts as we put our hope in you more fully and develop generous hearts that worship you with our giving.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2024-10</title>
        <author>
            <name>Asaph Yuan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages/2024-10.html"/>
        <id>https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages/2024-10.html</id>

        <updated>2024-10-07T00:32:15-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Things to write about: Halloween for kids-what is the proper response? Dr&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Things to write about:<br>Halloween for kids-what is the proper response?<br>Dr Jekyll and mr hyde romans 7, the christian response to sin and how to deal with sin after conversion. We are meant to grow in our faith and continually die to ourselves<br>Picture of dorian gray: our sin is not hidden before God<br>1b-dream: I was assigned first base, the attention comes and is not a reason to say no, nor is it right to shirk responsibility <br>Boston: for mission and friends</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2024-08</title>
        <author>
            <name>Asaph Yuan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages/august-2024.html"/>
        <id>https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages/august-2024.html</id>

        <updated>2024-09-28T20:31:04-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    What is God saying to me in this season?- Time with God&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p dir="ltr">What is God saying to me in this season?-</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation">Time with God in the morning</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation"><span style="color: var(--text-primary-color); font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Reading</span></p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation">You’re only human</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation">On fatherhood</p>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation">Enjoy time with Bea before the baby comes</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation">Build community</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation">Prayer and worship</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation">Casting the whole of your care [all your anxieties, all your worries, all your concerns, once and for all] on Him, for He cares for you affectionately and cares about you watchfully. - 1 Peter 5:7</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr" role="presentation">Remember eternity</p>
</li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2024-09</title>
        <author>
            <name>Asaph Yuan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages/september-2024-2.html"/>
        <id>https://asaphy.github.io/gh-pages/september-2024-2.html</id>

        <updated>2024-09-28T20:30:55-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    What is God saying to me in this season?- Pray about what&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p dir="ltr">What is God saying to me in this season?-</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Pray about what is next after our lease is up</li>
<li dir="ltr">Establish healthy habits with God as a family</li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
